



Determination

Set Up Objectives

Decision Making

Public Speaking





Making Mobile Applications Based Database



Microsoft Office 2013



Mikrotik Certification





Indonesia



English



- Jl. Kauman, Ngabar Kraton, Pasuruan
- github.com/bud1purwanto budi.purwanto15@gmail.com
- Budi Purwanto
- 085233233770

CURRICULUM VITAE

BUDI PURWANTO, S.Tr.Kom

Informatics Engineering of State Polytechnic of Malang



Self Description

I am able to work under pressure, work in a team or individually, I really like working with many people and also able to handle many people when they have problems regarding office work matters or not. And lastly, I care about the people I work with. I think I have adequate education and work experience. Besides, I'm always enthusiastic about what I do. This will make a positive contribution to the company's growth.



PERSONAL INFO

Name : Budi Purwanto

Place of Birth : Pasuruan

Date of Birth : January 16, 1997

Gender : **Male** Religion : **Islam**



EDUCATION

2015-2019 Politeknik Negeri Malang

D4-Teknik Informatika IPK 3.64

26

EXPERIENCE

Work Experience PT. Trias Sentosa, Tbk.

2019 - Present SAP ABAP Developer SQL Developer Organization Experience Lembaga Pers Mahasiswa Kompen 2017-2018

2017-2018 Member



SKILL & EXPERTISE

Design

Video Editing

MS. Word

MS. Excel

Powerpoint

SAP ABAP

SQL Server

PHP

JavaScript

Java Mobile

BUDI PURWANTO

Pasuruan, East Java · 0852-3223-3770

Budi.purwanto15@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/bud1purwanto · @bud1purwanto

A bachelor degree of majoring in Information Technology from State Politechnic of Malang. I am able to work under pressure, work in a team or individually, I really like working with many people and also able to handle many people when they have problems regarding office work matters or not. And lastly, I care about the people I work with. I think I have adequate education and work experience. Besides, I'm always enthusiastic about what I do. This will make a positive contribution to the company's growth.

EXPERIENCE

2019 SEPTEMBER-NOW

SR. ABAP DEVELOPER, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this company, I'm working with ERP software named SAP (System Application and Processing) as SAP ABAP Developer. As a SAP ABAP Developer, I am responsible to created or provided by SAP's internal functional consultant based on RICEF or functional specification, I write code using the ABAP programming language until it becomes a program that can be used.

Job Desc:

- SAP Business Improvement Full Life Cycle, develop the program according to the WRICEF that has been made by functional.
- Liaise with functional to meet business requirements.
- Optimization code for handling huge data.
- Create technical design.
- Help functional team to investigate stories about standard transaction.
- Develop and maintain SAP FICO, MM, PM, PP, QM and SD
- ABAP Skills: BDC, BAPI, BAdI, Smartforms, etc.
- Debug and SQL trace to solve issues.
- Interfacing Download SAP to Other Platform.

List Project that I Participated:

2022 JULY- PRESENT

DIGITAL BOARDROOM, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do development programs to display data based on the RICEF that has been created, where the data is GP data from our company.

2022 JANUARY – 2022 AUGUST

SAP & NON-SAP IMPLEMENTATION FOR CPP#1 & OPP#7, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do program development where I create a more dynamic program concept because the previous program required to make program changes (static) every time there are new production line implemention.

• 2022 APRIL – 2022

REPORT CAPITAL EXPENDITURES (CAPEX), PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do development programs for the costs incurred by the company to purchase, maintain and repair fixed assets/long-term assets.

• 2021 SEPTEMBER - 2021 JULY

BUSSINESS ANALYTICS (OLAP 2.0) - PRODUCTION REPORT, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do development program to display prodution data to be downloaded to SQL and displayed to Power BI.

2021 MARCH – 2021 AUGUST

BUSSINESS ANALYTICS (OLAP 2.0) - SALES REPORT, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do development program to display sales and GP data to be downloaded to SQL and displayed to Power BI.

2020 SEPTEMBER – 2021 MARCH

REPORT SUBCONTRACTING INTERCOMPANY, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility as SAP ABAP whose job is to do development programs to simplify transactions for Inter Company (Using BAPI or BDC).

2019 OCTOBER- NOW

SQL DEVELOPER, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this company, I'm alsi working as SQL Developer. I write code using SQL programming language with SSMS (SQL Server Management Studio) on-demand to help them get some coherent data.

List Project that I Participated:

• 2019 NOVEMBER- 2020 MARCH

WASTE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have the responsibility to do development programs to conduct transactions and report company waste data (Table, View and Stored Procedure).

• 2019 OCTOBER – 2019 NOVEMBER

IT INVENTORY, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have the responsibility to do development programs and testing.

2018 AUGUST – 2018 SEPTEMBER

INTERN, PT. PELABUHAN INDONESIA III (PERSERO)

PT Pelabuhan Indonesia (Persero) is a company engaged in logistics, especially port management and development. In this project, I have the responsibility to develop a website program to manage the company's assets.

EDUCATION

2015 SEPTEMBER – 2019 JULY

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, STATE POLYTECHNIC OF MALANG

Bachelor of Information Technology

SKILLS

- Strong sense of responsibility
- Eager to Learn
- Adaptive
- Communicative
- Have the same strength Individual or Team Work
- Analyze and Design Information System
- SAP ABAP
- SQL Developer
- Bussiness Analytic
- Design